守候于此天昏黑
I have waited for the day
誓要驱逐贪狼回
To send this greedy wolf away
神秘的魔法助我为神
Now the magic is my salvation
雄伟缭绕据于我身
Gather close in my protection
定 要 守护这营地!
We will stand for Everfree!
仰望那自然的恩赐，荣美而华丽
Behold the beauty of nature in all its glory
不惧那贪婪之人眉睫翘
No need to fear the vultures at the door
我会守护你 战至最后
Right here you have me to protect you
于荆之壁怒吼
Within these walls of thorns
为森灵地 永不沦落!
For Everfree for evermore!
前方的战火燃我眉
They have come into our domain
铁链之下吾土危
Here to seal our camp in chains
但我们守护它代代至深
But we have held it for generations
混乱只不过是须臾之时
This is just a complication
定 要 保卫这营地!
We will stand for Everfree!
相信我 一切不会辜负
Trust in me, this is for your own good
不要颤巍
Don't be afraid
自然伴吾身
Nature is our friend
围绕我们不止美丽繁华
All of this beauty that surrounds us
花朵的美丽 是自卫的伪装
Every lovely bloom designed to defend
来啊 放马都过来！
Let them come! Just let them try!
才不会轻易退下来！
I'm not about to say goodbye!
营地会于此永驻万世
This camp will be here throughout the ages
被世界纪录于广阔历史
Written into the history pages
定 要 保卫这营地！
We will stand for Everfree!